

I am a computer engineer who is passionate about game development in different genres and interested in the implementation of Serious Games. I am an active participant in research activities, particularly in the areas of software development, video game development within the educational sector. I was part of the first Jr. Unity Developer Bootcamp developed by Generation Colombia with the support of Unity.

CONTACT INFORMATION



Bogotá, Colombia



gaby030300@hotmail.com



+573024597568



https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabriela-bohorquez-ramirez-0267591bb/



https://gaby030300.github.io

EDUCATION

- Universidad Santo Tomás Computer Engineering, 2022
- Universidad Internacional de La Rioja
 (UNIR) Master's Degree in Industries 4.0
- Unity Jr. Developer Bootcamp Generation Colombia

LANGUAGES

Language English Upper Intermediate (B2)
Speaking: Upper Intermediate (B2) |
Writing: Advance (C1).
Language Spanish Native Speaker (C2)
Speaking: Native Speaker (C2) |
Writing: Native Speaker (C2).

CERTIFICATIONS

- Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate
- Unity Essentials Junior Programmer
- Introduction to videogames with Unreal Engine
- · Artificial Intelligence in Unreal Engine
- Creation of online multiplayer in Unreal Engine

EXPERIENCE

Young Researcher - Santo Tomás University

Apr 2020 - Nov 2021

 Part of the GreenTIC research group, where I participated in the development of 10 publications in topics such as: strengthening logical mathematical thinking and enabling internet Access for populations with limited internet Access through conversational agents.

Technology Analyst - Famisanar EPS

May 2022 - January 2023

- Migration of user applications related to health administrative services to supported technologies: Vue.js
 Vuetify.
- Coding of user stories following defined architecture standards.
- Correct quality errors and document solutions to ensure the development of specific functionalities and requirements.

Junior Game Programmer (Unity / Unreal Engine)- Streamline Studios

Feb 2022 - currently

 Writing clear, functional, documented and maintainable code according to the game design documentation, adhering to programming standards set.

SKILLS

- Research / Projects
- Unity / C# (Intermediate)
- Unreal Engine / C++ (Beginner)
- Leadership
- Game Development
- Game Design